# En-Rong Tsai

Email: enrong.tsai@gapp.nthu.edu.tw

Mobile: +886-978-508-523LinkedIn | Github | Facebook

# Introduction



I am currently a graduate student in Integration & Collaboration Lab in NTHU supervised by Prof. Wei-Chang Yeh. The experiences I obtained from the lab work equipped me with skills of large scale optimization, soft computing, and deep learning using a variety of frameworks and programming languages, such as Pytorch, Python, C++, etc. Currently, I am working on Deep Face Recognition problems. Especially, solving the posevariant issues limited by extreme profile views. I am actively searching for intern opportunities in the fields of computer vision and machine learning.

# **EDUCATION**

### National Tsing Hua University

• Master of Science in Industrial Engineering

# National Chung Cheng University

\* Bachelor of Arts in Economics

Hsinchu, Taiwan Aug. 2018 - Present Chiayi, Taiwan Sep. 2012 - Jun. 2016

#### RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

#### Integration & collaboration Lab:

• May 2019 - Present

My MS thesis entitled Improved Training Loss Function For Pose-Robust Deep Face Recognition. Our research base on Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN) proposes an Improved Training Loss Function for solving the pose-variant issues that confront by extreme profile views. The proposed loss function can dynamically manipulate the learning weight correspond to the yaw degrees of the profile images with the supervision of state-of-the-art learning loss to ensure both discriminability and the large profile learning. Furthermore, due to the attribute of alleviating imbalanced training data issues, we expect the contribution of our research can extend to address other fine-grained object classification problems.

• Dec. 2019

Invited by Advisor, I was honored to give a lecture in IEEM1080105 talk about the recent progress of deep learning based face recognition, especially the evolution of loss function design in the past five years, and demonstrate the leap forward of our current research.

#### Knowledge Engineering Lab:

• Aug. 2018 - Feb. 2019

Utilize the text mining approach, including TFIDF and K-means clustering, to manipulate the Knowledge Acquisition process and analyze the research trend of virtual reality exposure therapy (VRET) in phobia treatment from 2008 to 2018.

• Aug. 2018 - Feb. 2019

Responsible for establishing a virtual reality environment for VRET therapy research on driving phobia. The research is in collaboration with Chang Gung Hospital and uCare Medical Electronics.

# Teaching & Leadership:

- Sep. 2009 Present
  - 10+ years of instructor experience with training certificate for True Jesus Church Religious Education. (Teaching experience from elementary school children to high school teenagers.)
- Sep. 2012 Jun. 2016

Participated in the Living Water Fellowship\* as the President and Event General Coordinator for 2+ years.

\*Living Water Fellowship is a Christian joint club of Six Universities in the Chiayi region concerning non-profit social services and sharing religious faith.

# Awards and Achievements

- Sep. 2012 Aug. 2013
  Associated in the department badminton team and won the champion of the 2012 economics cup.
- Feb. 2015 Jun. 2015

  Participate in Industrial economic startup competition, our group won 2nd place in the overall ranking, and 1st place in campus non-profit startup categories.

# $S{\tt KILLS}$

- Programming Languages: Python, C++, C#, VimL, LaTex, HTML 5, CSS, Javascript
- Frameworks & Develops Tools: PyTorch, OpenCV, Vim, Tmux, Github, Ubuntu Server, Docker, GCP Compute Engine
- Languages: TOEIC: 750/990 (2012)